PALUDGNACH MATTEO

Full-Stack Software developer

SKILLS

FRONTEND

sveltekit - tailwind - flutter

BACKEND

typescript - golang

DEVOPS

github actions - argocd - kubernetes

DATABASES

postgres - redis - mongodb

CONTACTS

1 +39 3518853376

☑ paludgnachmatteo.dev@gmail.com

portfolio.mp281x.xyz

github.com/MP281X

Moimacco (UD)

LANGUAGES

ITALIAN - native

ENGLISH - B2

SUMMARY

For several years I have been deeply passionate about web, application and API development by utilizing technologies such as Typescript, SvelteKit, Flutter, Golang, Postgres, Redis and MongoDB.

Additionally I have an interest in DevOps, employing technologies like Docker and Kubernetes, UI/UX design and project planning.

I am punctual and reliable due to my initiative and organizational skills, and I endeavor to consistently bring fresh ideas to the table.

WORK EXPERIENCE

BIZAWAY (stage)
Backend Developer

12/06/2023 - 04/08/2023 Spilimbergo (IT)

NORDEST SERVIZI (stage)

17/01/2022 - 29/01/2022

System Engineer

Tavagnacco (IT)

EDUCATION

ITS Alto Adriatico 2022 - 2024

Final vote: -- EQF: 5

Tecnico Superiore Cloud Developer

ISIS A. Malignani 2017 - 2022

Final vote: 68 EQF: 4

Diploma in IT and Telecomunications